https://www.aligned-assets.co.uk/about-us/internet-privacy-and-cookies-policy/

close
01483 717950 We’re committed to safeguarding the privacy of all our website visitors Solutions arrow_right_alt Contact Us arrow_right_altCase StudiesProduct CatalogueUPRNHome » About us » Privacy & cookies policyAt Aligned Assets Limited we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our websites visitors. This policy explains what happens to any personal data that you either provide us with, or that we collect as a result of your visit to our website. It also explains how we use cookies on our site. We do update this policy from time to time so please do review it regularly.Information we collectIn running and maintaining our website we may collect and process the following data about you:Information about your use of our site including details of your visits such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.Information provided voluntarily by you, e.g when you register for an event, request further information or make a purchase.Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means.Cookie PolicyThis site uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics.As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at the About Cookies website which offers guidance for all modern browsers.Use of your informationWe use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you. In addition to this we may use it for one or more of the following purposes:To provide information to you that you request from us relating to our products or services.To provide information to you relating to other products that may be of interest to you. This will only be provided when you have consented to receive such information.To inform you of any changes to our website, services or goods and products.If you have previously purchased goods or services from us we may provide you with details of similar goods or services, or other goods and services, that you may be interested in.We never give your details to third parties to use for marketing purposes. Storing your personal dataIn operating our website it may become necessary to transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the European Union for processing and storing. By providing your personal data to us, you agree to this transfer, storing and processing. We do our utmost to ensure that all reasonable steps are taken to make sure that your data is stored securely.Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet is not totally secure and on occasion such information can be intercepted. We cannot guarantee the security of data that you choose to send us electronically, sending such information is entirely at your own risk.Disclosing your informationWe will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this privacy policy and in the circumstances detailed below:In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer.Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information.To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud.Third party linksOn occasion we include links to third parties on this website. Where we provide a link it does not mean that we endorse or approve that site’s policy towards visitor privacy. You should review their privacy policy before sending them any personal data.Contacting usPlease do not hesitate to contact us regarding any matter relating to this privacy and cookies policy using the Contact us page. Contact us Product catalogue
SolutionsLLPG solution for local authoritiesLSG solution for local authoritiesAddressBase Premium gazetteer for emergency servicesAddressBase Premium for energy and water utilitiesAddress searching and management for organisationsAddress matching & cleansingStreet Naming & Numbering for local authoritiesLocation based augmented realityCloud based hosted solutionsNational addressing solutions for all countriesServicesBS7666 consultancyProduct supportBS7666 and product trainingCustomer portalAnnual customer user group eventsCustomer portalNewsLatest newsEventsCase studiesAbout usWho we areOur officesOur teamCareersOur partnersOur customersPrivacy & cookies policyContact us
